{"name": "74F  2017-4 \u5b98\u7f51 ", "questions": [{"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "1. Marcus's favorite casserole recipe requires 3 eggs and makes 6 servings. Marcus will modify the recipe by using 5 eggs and increasing all other ingredients in the recipe proportionally. What is the total number of servings the modified recipe will make?", "choices": {"A": "6", "B": "8", "C": "10", "D": "12", "E": "15"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "2. The 35-member History Club is meeting to choose a student government representative. The members decide that the representative, who will be chosen at random, CANNOT be any of the 3 officers of the club. What is the probability that Hiroko, who is a member of the club but NOT an officer, will be chosen?", "choices": {"A": "0", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "3. For what value of x is the equation true?", "choices": {"A": "2", "B": "4", "C": "11", "D": "16", "E": "44"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "4. Let the function f be defined as . What is the value of f(3)?", "choices": {"A": "-18", "B": "-26", "C": "-33", "D": "-60", "E": "-75"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "5. A wallet containing 5 five-dollar bills, 7 ten-dollar bills, and 8 twenty-dollar bills is found and returned to its owner. The wallet\u2019s owner will reward the finder with 1 bill drawn randomly from the wallet. What is the probability that the bill drawn will be a twenty-dollar bill?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "6. The ABC Book Club charges a $40 monthly fee, plus $2 per book read in that month. The Easy Book Club charges a $35 monthly fee, plus $3 per book read in that month. For each club, how many books must be read in 1 month for the total charges from each club to be equal?", "choices": {"A": "1", "B": "4", "C": "5", "D": "6", "E": "75"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "7. In parallelogram ABCD below, AC  is a diagonal, the measure of \u2220ABC is 40\u00b0, and the measure of \u2220ACD is 57\u00b0. What is the measure of \u2220CAD ?", "choices": {"A": "40\u00b0", "B": "57\u00b0", "C": "77\u00b0", "D": "83\u00b0", "E": "97\u00b0"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "8. When , what is the value of  ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "2", "C": "", "D": "5", "E": "10"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "9. In the standard (x, y) coordinate plane, what is the midpoint of the line segment that has endpoints (3,8) and (1,-4) ?", "choices": {"A": "(-2, -12)", "B": "(-1, 6)", "C": "", "D": "( 2,  2)", "E": "( 4, -12)"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "10. The fluctuation of water depth at a pier is shown in the figure below. One of the following values gives the positive difference, in feet, between the greatest water depth and the least water depth shown in this graph. Which value is it?", "choices": {"A": "3", "B": "6", "C": "9", "D": "12", "E": "19"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "11. What is the slope of the line through (-2,1) and (2,-5) in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "1", "C": "-1", "D": "", "E": "-4"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "12. In Cherokee County, the fine for speeding is $17 for each mile per hour the driver is traveling over the posted speed limit. In Cherokee County, Kirk was fined $221 for speeding on a road with a posted speed limit of 30 mph. Kirk was fined for traveling at what speed, in miles per hour?", "choices": {"A": "13", "B": "17", "C": "43", "D": "47", "E": "60"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "13. What is the sum of the solutions of the 2 equations below?                                      8x = 12                              2x + 10 = 22", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "9", "D": "10", "E": ""}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "14. The average of 5 distinct scores has the same value as the median of the 5 scores. The sum of the 5 scores is 420. What is the sum of the 4 scores that are NOT the median?", "choices": {"A": "315", "B": "320", "C": "336", "D": "350", "E": "360"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "15. What is the value of the expression below?", "choices": {"A": "-18", "B": "-2", "C": "0", "D": "2", "E": "18"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "16. Which of the following expressions is equivalent to  ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "17. In the standard (x, y) coordinate plane, what is the slope of the line given by the equation 4x = 7y + 5 ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "4", "E": "7"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "18. For which of the following conditions will the sum of integers m and n always be an odd integer?", "choices": {"A": "m is an odd integer.", "B": "n is an odd integer.", "C": "m and n are both odd integers.", "D": "m and n are both even integers.", "E": "m is an odd integer and n is an even integer."}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "19. The lengths of the 2 legs of right triangle \u25b3ABC shown below are given in inches. The midpoint of  AB is how many inches from A?", "choices": {"A": "16", "B": "20", "C": "21", "D": "28", "E": "40"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "20. In \u25b3DEF, the length of DE is  inches, and the length of EF is 3 inches. If it can be determined, what is the length, in inches, of  DF  ?", "choices": {"A": "3", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "Cannot be determined from the given information."}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "21. Laura plans to paint the 8-foot-high rectangular walls of her room, and before she buys paint she needs to know the area of the wall surface to be painted. Two walls are 10 feet wide, and the other 2 walls are 15 feet wide. The combined area of the 1 window and the 1 door in her room is 60 square feet. What is the area, in square feet, of the wall surface Laura plans to paint?", "choices": {"A": "200", "B": "340", "C": "360", "D": "390", "E": "400"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "22. The length of a rectangle is 5 inches longer than the width. The perimeter of the rectangle is 40 inches. What is the width of the rectangle, in inches?", "choices": {"A": "7.5", "B": "8", "C": "15", "D": "16", "E": "17.5"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "23. 8% of 60 is of what number?", "choices": {"A": "0.96", "B": "12", "C": "24", "D": "240", "E": "3,750"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "24. Armin is trying to decide whether to buy a season pass to his college basketball team\u2019s 20 home games this season. The cost of an individual ticket is $14, and the cost of a season pass is $175. The season pass will admit Armin to any home basketball game at no additional cost. What is the minimum number of home basketball games Armin must attend this season in order for the cost of a season pass to be less than the total cost of buying an individual ticket for each game he attends?", "choices": {"A": "8", "B": "9", "C": "12", "D": "13", "E": "20"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "25. ", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": " "}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "26. A circle in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane has center C(-1, 2) and passes through A(2, 6). Line segment AB is a diameter of this circle. What are the coordinates of point B ?", "choices": {"A": "(-6, -2)", "B": "(-5, -1)", "C": "(-4, -2)", "D": "(4, 2)", "E": "(5, 10)"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "27. Which of the following expressions is a factor of  ?", "choices": {"A": "x - 4", "B": "x + 4", "C": "x + 64", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "28. The average of a list of 4 numbers is 90.0. A new list of 4 numbers has the same first 3 numbers as the original list, but the fourth number in the original list is 80, and the fourth number in the new list is 96. What is the average of this new list of numbers?", "choices": {"A": "90.0", "B": "91.5", "C": "94.0", "D": "94.5", "E": "94.8"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "29. The number a is located at -2.5 on the number line below. One of the following number lines shows the location of  . Which number line is it?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "30. Maria ordered a pizza. She ate only of it and gave the remaining pizza to her 3 brothers. What fraction of the whole pizza will each of Maria\u2019s brothers receive, if they share the remaining pizza equally?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "31. The number 1,001 is the product of the prime numbers 7, 11, and 13. Knowing this, what is the prime factorization of 30,030 ?", "choices": {"A": "3 \u00b7 7 \u00b7 10 \u00b7 13", "B": "30 \u00b7 7 \u00b7 11 \u00b7 13", "C": "2 \u00b7 5 \u00b7 7 \u00b7 11 \u00b7 13", "D": "3 \u00b7 7 \u00b7 10 \u00b7 11 \u00b7 13", "E": "2 \u00b7 3 \u00b7 5 \u00b7 7 \u00b7 11 \u00b7 13"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "32. Use the following information to answer questions 32-34.Mikea, an intern with the Parks and Recreation Department, is developing a proposal for the new trapezoidal Springdale Park. The figure below shows her scale drawing of the proposed park with 3 side lengths and the radius of the merry-go-round given in inches. In Mikea\u2019s scale drawing, 1 inch represents 1.5 feet.32. What is the area, in square inches, of the scale drawing of the park ?", "choices": {"A": "448", "B": "544", "C": "640", "D": "672", "E": "1,088"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "33. Use the following information to answer questions 32-34.Mikea, an intern with the Parks and Recreation Department, is developing a proposal for the new trapezoidal Springdale Park. The figure below shows her scale drawing of the proposed park with 3 side lengths and the radius of the merry-go-round given in inches. In Mikea\u2019s scale drawing, 1 inch represents 1.5 feet.33. Mikea\u2019s proposal includes installing a fence on the perimeter of the park. What is the perimeter, in feet, of the park?", "choices": {"A": "84", "B": "88", "C": "104", "D": "126", "E": "156"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "34. Use the following information to answer questions 32-34.Mikea, an intern with the Parks and Recreation Department, is developing a proposal for the new trapezoidal Springdale Park. The figure below shows her scale drawing of the proposed park with 3 side lengths and the radius of the merry-go-round given in inches. In Mikea\u2019s scale drawing, 1 inch represents 1.5 feet.34. The length of the south side of the park is what percent of the length of the north side?", "choices": {"A": "112%", "B": "124%", "C": "", "D": "175%", "E": "250%"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "35. Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.The Smith family is planning to build a 3-room cabin which consists of 2 bedrooms (BR) and 1 living room (LR). Shown below are the rectangular floor plan (left figure) and a side view of the cabin (right figure). In the side view, the roof forms an isosceles triangle (\u25b3ABC) , the walls are perpendicular to the level floor (ED)\uff0cAC  \u2225 ED ,  F is the midpoint of AC and BF \u22a5 AC .During the week the Smiths plan to roof the cabin, there is a 20% chance of rain each day.35. Mr. Smith plans to build a 3-foot-wide walkway around the outside of the cabin, as shown in the floor plan. What will be the area, in square feet, of the top surface of the walkway?", "choices": {"A": "171", "B": "324", "C": "360", "D": "396", "E": "720"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "36. Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.The Smith family is planning to build a 3-room cabin which consists of 2 bedrooms (BR) and 1 living room (LR). Shown below are the rectangular floor plan (left figure) and a side view of the cabin (right figure). In the side view, the roof forms an isosceles triangle(\u25b3ABC) , the walls are perpendicular to the level floor (ED)\uff0cAC  \u2225 ED ,  F is the midpoint of AC and BF \u22a5 AC .During the week the Smiths plan to roof the cabin, there is a 20% chance of rain each day.36. Mrs. Smith will install a ceiling fan in each room of the cabin and will place curtains over the 4 windows. Each of the ceiling fans has a price of $52.00. The price of curtains for each small window (S) is $39.50, and the price of curtains for the large window (L) is twice that for the small window. Based on this information, which of the following values is closest to the total price Mrs. Smith will pay for curtains and ceiling fans?", "choices": {"A": "$262", "B": "$302", "C": "$341", "D": "$354", "E": "$393"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "37. Use the following information to answer questions 35-37.The Smith family is planning to build a 3-room cabin which consists of 2 bedrooms (BR) and 1 living room (LR). Shown below are the rectangular floor plan (left figure) and a side view of the cabin (right figure). In the side view, the roof forms an isosceles triangle (\u25b3ABC) , the walls are perpendicular to the level floor (ED)\uff0cAC  \u2225 ED ,  F is the midpoint of AC and BF \u22a5 AC .During the week the Smiths plan to roof the cabin, there is a 20% chance of rain each day.37. Mr. and Mrs. Smith plan to roof the cabin on 2 consecutive days. Assuming that the chance of rain is independent of the day, what is the probability that it will rain both days?", "choices": {"A": "0.04", "B": "0.08", "C": "0.16", "D": "0.2", "E": "0.4"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "38. Which of the following expressions, when evaluated, equals an irrational number?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": " ", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "39. A line through the origin and (10,4) is shown in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane below. The acute angle between the line and the positive x-axis has measure \u03b8 .\nWhat is the value of tan \u03b8 ?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "40. The equation  |2x - 8| + 3 = 5  has 2 solutions. Those solutions are equal to the solutions to which of the following pairs of equations", "choices": {"A": "  2x - 5 =  5-2x - 5 = -5", "B": "  2x - 8 = 2-2x - 8 = 2", "C": "    2x - 8 = 8-(2x - 8) = 8", "D": "  2x - 8 = 2-(2x - 8) = 8", "E": "  2x - 8 = 2-(2x - 8) = 2"}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "41. The frequency chart below shows the cumulative number of Ms. Hernandez\u2019s science students whose test scores fell within certain score ranges. All test scores are whole numbers. How many students have a test score in the interval 71-80 ?", "choices": {"A": "1", "B": "6", "C": "8", "D": "12", "E": "13"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "42. The number of decibels, d , produced by an audio source can be modeled by the equation  , where  is the sound intensity of the audio source and K is a constant. How many decibels are produced by an audio source whose sound intensity is 1,000 times the value of  K ?", "choices": {"A": "4", "B": "30", "C": "40", "D": "100", "E": "10,000"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "43. Mario inlays basketball on a town league team. The table below gives Mario\u2019s scoring statistics for last season. How many points did Mario score playing basketball last season?", "choices": {"A": "129", "B": "190", "C": "213", "D": "330", "E": "380"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "44. The graph of is in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane. Which of the following transformations, when applied to the graph of  ,results in the graph of is ?", "choices": {"A": "Translation to the right 6 coordinate units", "B": "Translation to the left 6 coordinate units", "C": "Translation up 6 coordinate units", "D": "Translation down 6 coordinate units", "E": "Reflection across the line x = 6"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "45. Toby wants to find the volume of a solid toy soldier. He fills a rectangular container 8 cm long, 6 cm wide, and 10 cm high with water to a depth of 4 cm. Toby totally submerges the toy soldier in the water. The height of the water with the submerged toy soldier is 6.6 cm. Which of the following is closest to the volume, in cubic centimeters, of the toy soldier?", "choices": {"A": "125", "B": "156", "C": "192", "D": "208", "E": "317"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "46. A box in the shape of a cube has an interior side length of 18 inches and is used to ship a right circular cylinder with a radius of 6 inches and a height of 12 inches. The interior of the box not occupied by the cylinder is filled with packing material. Which of the following numerical expressions gives the number of cubic inches of the box filled with packing material \uff1f", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "47. A room has a rectangular floor that is 15 feet by 21 feet. What is the area of the floor in square yards ?", "choices": {"A": "24", "B": "35", "C": "36", "D": "105", "E": "144"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "48. ABC Cabs and Tary Taxicabs both have an initial fare of a whole number of dollars for 1 passenger. The fare increases a whole number of dollars at each whole number of miles traveled. The graphs below show the 1-passenger fares, in dollars, for both cab companies for trips up to 6 miles. When the fares of the 2 cab companies are compared, what is the cheaper fare for a 5-mile trip?", "choices": {"A": "$ 8", "B": "$ 9", "C": "$10", "D": "$ 11", "E": "$12"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "49. The graph of a function y = f(x) consists of 3 line segments. The graph and the coordinates of the endpoints of the 3 line segments are shown in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane below. What is the area, in square coordinate units, of the region bounded by the graph of y = f(x) the positive  y-axis, and the positive x-axis?", "choices": {"A": "10", "B": "13", "C": "14", "D": "15", "E": "20"}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "50. The sum of 2 positive numbers is 151. The lesser number is 19 more than the square root of the greater number. What is the value of the greater number minus the lesser number ?", "choices": {"A": "19", "B": "66", "C": "85", "D": "91", "E": "121"}, "correct": "D"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "51. The list of numbers 41, 35, 30, X, Y, 15 has a median of 25. The mode of the list of numbers is 15. To the nearest whole number, what is the mean of the list ?", "choices": {"A": "20", "B": "25", "C": "26", "D": "27", "E": "30"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "52. You are given the following system of equations:                                                                               where r, s, and t are integers. For which of the following will there be more than one  (x, y) solution, with real-number coordinates, for the system?", "choices": {"A": "0\">", "B": "0\">", "C": "", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "53. The 3rd and 4th terms of an arithmetic sequence are 13 and 18, respectively. What is the 50th term sequence?", "choices": {"A": "248", "B": "250", "C": "253", "D": "258", "E": "263"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "54. One of the following graphs in the standard (x, y) coordinate plane is the graph of  over the domain . Which one ?", "choices": {"A": " ", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": " "}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "55. What is the period at the function ", "choices": {"A": "\u03c0", "B": "2\u03c0", "C": "4\u03c0", "D": "", "E": ""}, "correct": "E"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "56. At the school carnival, Mike will play a game in which he will toss a penny, a nickel, and a dime at the same time. He will be awarded 3 points for each coin that lands with heads faceup. Let the random variable x represent the total number of points awarded on any toss of the coins. What is the expected value of x ?", "choices": {"A": "1", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "6", "E": "9"}, "correct": "C"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "57. For what positive real value of k, if any, is the determinant of the matrix  equal to k? (Note: The determinant of matrix  equals ad - bc. )", "choices": {"A": "3", "B": "4", "C": "12", "D": "", "E": "There is no such value of k."}, "correct": "B"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "58. Given a positive integer n such that   , which of the following statements about n must be true? (Note: )", "choices": {"A": "When n is divided by 4, the remainder is 0.", "B": "When n is divided by 4, the remainder is 1.", "C": "When n is divided by 4t the remainder is 2.", "D": "When n is divided by 4, the remainder is 3.", "E": "Cannot be determined from the given information."}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "", "question": "59. For  , is true for all and only the values of  in which of the following sets?", "choices": {"A": "", "B": "", "C": "", "D": "", "E": "The empty set"}, "correct": "A"}, {"title": "", "name": "", "article": "<p><br/></p>", "question": "60. Ray  bisects \u2220LPM, the measure of \u2220LPM is 11x\u00b0\uff0c and the measure of\u2220LPK is (4x + 18)\u00b0 . What is the measure of \u2220KPM?", "choices": {"A": "12\u00b0", "B": " ", "C": "42\u00b0", "D": "", "E": "66\u00b0"}, "correct": "E"}]}